Indiana University Folklore Institute Material Culture papers, 1953-1984, bulk 1960-1981 C614
Indiana University Archives
- Student Papers (Box 1)
  - M/C 80/4 Cornwell, Tom. "Tradition of the Quarry Worker with Emphasis on Techniques and Tools Used" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F101, El-Shamy, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/5 Martin, Craig. "Pipes and Beakers: An Old German-American Tradition" (North America, U.S., Missouri, St. Louis), F220, Mary Ellen Lewis (previously Mary Ellen Brown), Polezoes (A.I.), 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/6 Garrity, Michelle. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Mary Ellen Lewis (previously Mary Ellen Brown), April 27, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/7 Fee, Kathryn. "Maple Syrup" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Parke County), F220, Mary Ellen Lewis (previously Mary Ellen Brown), Harrison (T.A.?), April 5, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/8 Cox, Anne-Marie. "Seat Weaving" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County), F391, Roberts, May 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/9 Edging, Thomas. "Hog Butchering" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Parke County), F220, Mary Ellen Lewis (previously Mary Ellen Brown), Phyllis Harrison (T.A.?), 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/10 Headley, Steve. "The Art of Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F220, Lewis (previously Mary Ellen Brown), April 14, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/11 Brown, Charles Clark. "Small Sawmills in Southern Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Dr. Warren Roberts, December 10, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/12 Zima, Debra. "Greek Cooking" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Porter County, Portage), F220, Lewis (previously Mary Ellen Brown), 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/13 Temme, Kimberly Marie. "Tatting, Crocheting, and Quilting: Linking the Past with the Present" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Vanderburgh County, Darmstadt & Evansille), F220, Lewis (previously Mary Ellen Brown), Gary Stanton (A.I.), April 6, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/14 Sitek, Frances Arlene. "A Brief Look at Folk Cookery" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Starke County, Knox), F101, El-Shamy, April 19, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/15 Kennedy, John. "An Analysis of Brewing in America" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Franklin County), F101, Zygas, August 13, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/16 Underhill, Kim. "Quiltmaking: A Fascinating Hobby" (North America, U.S., Missouri), F101, Roger Beatty, April 20, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/17 Duckworth, Virginia. "Geographic and Structural Comparisons of Two Barns in Central and Southern Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, November 7, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/18 Filburn, Mark. "John and Chris Filburn Barn," F220, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/19 VonBorstel, Donald W. "Fences," F220, Instructor Unknown, August 11, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/20 David, Randy A. "Folk and Pop Architecture of Eastern Indianapolis, F220, Instructor Unknown, April 29, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/21 Claxton, Karen. "411 North Park Avenue, Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 12, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/22 Elliot, Sandra. "So, You Live in the Harrell House," F220, Instructor Unknown, December 1, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/23 Schroeder, Lori. "Two Folk Houses in the United States, Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 12, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/24 Hartlieb, Sandra. "Houseboat Living: A Folklore Study", F220, Instructor Unknown, December 12, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/25 Swank, Aaron E. "Old Ways of Hunting and Trapping," F220, Jens Lund, December 12, 1975 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/26 Seeber, Tom. "Field Work Project," F220, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/27 Boring, Janice. "Preserving and Storing Vegetables," F220, Instructor Unknown, December 12, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/28 Endsley, Letitia. "American Quilting," F220, Kathy Lownds, November 11, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/29 Beach, Sandra S. "The Southern Indiana Quilt: A Folklore Collection Project," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 10, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/30 Reed, Judy. "Quilt-making," F220, Instructor Unknown, November 6, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/31 Morris, Deborah. "Embroidery," Class # Unknown, Kathy Figgen, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/1 Pancoast, Sandra L. "Taffy Making" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Pike County, Rumbletown), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 25, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/2 Parish, Fumiyo H. "Roasted on a Plough" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Lawrence County, Bedford), F101, Zygas, August 13, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/3 Colglazier, Mark. "Hamer's Mill: A Study of Traditional Architecture" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Lawrence County, Mitchell, Spring Mill State Park), F101, Zygas, August 13, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/4 Reichard, Katie. "German Christmas Cooking" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County, Indianapolis), F101, Zygas, August 30, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/5 Pennington, James M. "Covered Bridges in Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Parke County), F220, Instructor Unknown, December 12, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/6 Poling, Anita. "The Dulcimer: Then and Now" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County, Indianapolis), F220, Instructor Unknown, December 12, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/7 Brown, Robert Eugene. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County, Indianapolis), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 5, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/8 Renn, Leann. "Hog Butchering a Bailey Family Tradition" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Morgan County, Martinsville), F220, Johnson, April 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/9 Grames, Katie. "Traditional Foodways of Japan" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County, Indianapolis), F101, Johnson, April 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/10 Booker, Kimberly D. "A Man is his Craft" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Montgomery County, Crawfordsville), F220, Mr. Jens Lund, December 12, 1980 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/11 Spencer, Neal. "Fences" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Bloomington), F220, Doris Fanelli, Spring 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/12 Ward, Dewayne. "The Old School House" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, May 3, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/13 Harris, Julie. "Analysis of Folklore Project on Weaving," F101, Instructor Unknown, December 14, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/14 Alexander, Capri. "The Craft of Quilting," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 5, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/15 Salzmann, Jean. "Quilting as a Traditional Craft, and its Historical Changes," F220, Instructor Unknown, November 20, 1981 (Box 8)
    (Two analog audio cassette tapes removed and stored separately in box 9)
  - M/C 81/16 Kuchler, Kathleen. "An Architectural Study of the First Brick Structures in Nashville, Indiana (with complimentary history)," F220, Alice Morrison Mordoh, May 5, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/17 Miller, Anna. No Title, F220, Stahl, Fall 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/18 Schutter, Dave. "Sheep Shearing," PSY101, Professor Stahl, December 1, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/19 Vaughn, Sharon. "Harve Hildebrand, Scrimshander: A Folklife Study," F220, Stahl, Spring 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/20 Lamie, Philip. "Donavan Hostetler and His Dowsing Rod," Class # Unknown, Alice Morrison Mordoh, November 20, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/21 Clark, Mace. "Corrective Horseshoeing: Traditionally Learned and Passed on in Central Indiana," Class # Unknown, Elaine Lawless, December 7, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/22 Cannon, Tamara. "Dolls," F220, Instructor Unknown, December 1, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/23 Hage, Barb. "Folklore Collection: Foodways of My Family," F101, Johnson/Conforth, April 4, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/24 Cassini, P. No Title, Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, May 5, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/25 Griggs, Richard W. "Moonshining: A Fine Art of Folklore," F220, Eric Montenyohl, Fall 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/26 Hammond, Nancy J. "Embroidery Through the Generations," F101, Instructor Unknown, April 2, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/27 Markey, Stephen. "The Folk Costume of a College Campus 'The Preppy Style'," Class # Unknown, Bruce Conforth, April 3, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 81/28 Dambrose, Mike. "The Custom Made Suit," F101, Lawless, July 9, 1981 (Box 8)
  - M/C 82/1 Jackson, Rhea D. "Quilt Construction: How Methods May Have Changed" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F101, Instructor Unknown, April 9, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/2 Houts, Sarah. "Collection Proposal" (North America, U.S., Kalamazoo, Michigan), F101, Instructor Unknown, February 11, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/3 Groff, Daryl C. "Building Along Yellow Creek: A Study in Barn Architecture" (North America, U.S., Goshen, Indiana), Class Unknown, Ervin Beck, December 9, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/4 Gary, James. "Mr. Gary's Barn: An Item of Folk Architecture," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 8, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/5 Hettinger, Anthony P. "A Traditional American Barn," F101, April 7, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/6 Wenger, John. "A Collection of Goshen, Indiana, Barn Architecture," Class # Unknown, Prof. Ervin Beck, December 12, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/7 Dillman, Cary. "The Maple Sugar Process," F220, Paul Tyler, April 8, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/8 Ramsburg, Craig. "Armenian Cooking," F220, Instructor Unknown, April 5, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/9 Steckbeck, Jane. "From Sugar Water to Syrup: An Old and Delicious Process," F101, Kathi Figgen, April 8, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/10 Sommers, Dallas R. "The Folk Art of Argus Myers," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 14, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/11 Comer, Bernita A. "Quilting: Past and Present," F220, Dr. Stahl, Spring 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/12 Latif, Rosilawati. "Folk Costume - The 'Baju Kurung'," F100, Dr. William Johnson, April 10, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 82/13 Houts, Sarah. "Collection Projects: Quilting," F101, Johnson, April 8, 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/1 Wilson, Cynthia Lea (Cindy). 'Folklore Project 1" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Bloomfield) F220, Stahl, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/2 Ruh, Henry. "Quilting in Bloomington Monroe County Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F101, A. Mordoh, April 18, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/3 McDonald, Debra. "The Meier Saltbox House," F101, Mordoh, April 25, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/4 Morris, Anne J. "Barns of Johnson County," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 25, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/5 Pugh, Susan A. "Folk Architecture," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 25, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/6 Davis, Sharlee. "Foodways of a Folk Group," F101, McDowell, Fall 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/7 Norkunas, Martha. No Title, Class # Unknown, Warren Roberts, Spring 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/8 Beitman, James A. "An Interview with Mr. Roberts, A Sorghum Miller," F220, Dr. Glassie/Yens Lund, November 30, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/9 Harris Diane E. "The Art of Weaving," F101, Mordoh, April 4, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 83/10 Foreman, Lori. "The Interview Attire," F101, Mordoh, Spring 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/1 Voiles, Benjamin. "Growing & Making Sorghum Molasses" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Decatur County, Westport), F220, Instructor Unknown, Carrol L. Edwards (A.I.), November 21, 1974 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/2 Debbie, Olliver. "The Material Culture of Spinning" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F220, Instructor Unknown, Carol Edwards (A.I.?), July 27, 1978 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/4 Nail, Betty. "The Importance of Corn and Grist Mills in the 1800's" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Lawrence County, Mitchell), F101, Jack Williams, November 20, 1981 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/5 Schnaiter, Brad. "Slaughtering Hogs" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Morgan County, Martinsville), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/6 Johnson, Grace. "Morel Mushroom Hunting" (North America, U.S., Ohio, Millwood), F220, Instructor Unknown, Summer 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/7 Miles, Jeff D. "Moonshine" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F101, Instructor Unknown, April 25, 1983 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/8 Good, Kisti. "Folklore Project" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Clinton County, Frankfort - woodworking, carving), F101, McDowell, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/10 Moody, Tonya. "Homebrew - A Traditional Recipe" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County, Indianapolis), Introduction to American Folklore, Gary Stanton, May 2, 1980 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/11Witlow, Diane. "Folk Craft-Dutch" (North America, U.S., Indianapolis, Indiana), F220, Dolby-Stahl, April 19, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/12 Leighty, Vicki. "A Morgan County Rag Rug Weaver" (Frances McKee – Rag Rug Weaver, North America, U.S.) F391, A. Mordoh, February 8, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/13 Paulson, Susan P. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Munster, Indiana), F391, A. Mordoh, April 23, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/14 VandeWater, Steven M. "Southern Indiana Shotguns" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, A.M. Mordoh, April 23, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/15 Bass, Mary. "The Home Place: Family History of and Folk Architecture of the Home of Mary L. Bates (1875-1975)," F391, Alice Morrison-Mordoh, March 26, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/16 Schuman, Margaret. "Quilting with Opal Landis," F391, Mordoh, Spring 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/17 Murphy, Carolyn B. "Quilting Traditions as Carried on by the Descendants of Caroline Blume Huffer," F391, Mordoh, Spring 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/18 Deckard, Pamela E. "A 1 1/2 Story Dogtrot House of Log Construction with Additions and Renovation," F391, Instructor Unknown, March 26, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/19 Brandt, Amanda. "Geode Art," F391, Mordoh, April 7, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/20 Edmonds, Donna. "Field Projects," F220, Dolby-Stahl, April 19, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/21 Pruett, Patricia. "Indiana Limestone and the Folk Art of Stone Carving," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, March 3, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/22 Scott, Susan Shawn. No Title, F220, Professor Dolby-Stahl, October 2, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/23 Truex, Rick. "The Roles People Play in the Making of Blooding Pudding," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/24 Alexander, Dawn Marie. No Title, F220, Dolby-Stahl, Spring 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/25 Bridges, Anne. "Food Preservation," F391, Alice Mordoh, April 23, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/26 Cree, Sue Anne. "Folk Gardening of Southern Indiana," F391, Mordoh, Spring 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 84/27 Tiplick, Bob. "Folklore Analysis," Class # Unknown, Professor MacDowell, April 12, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/1 Gibbs, Diana. "Indiana Folklore Term Paper" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Hendricks County, Lizton), Indiana Folklore, Instructor Unknown, 1979 (Box 9)
    (Quarter inch analog open reel recording tape removed and stored separately in box 10)
  - M/C 85/2 Evans, Timothy (Tim). "Shotgun Houses in Bloomington, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F720, Instructor Unknown, 1981 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/3 Terry, Cedric. "The Subject of: Black Men's Hair Styles"(North America, U.S., Indiana, Lake County, Gary), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1979 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/4 Barger, Carolyn. "Droodles." (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F101, Johnson, 1979 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/5 Brown, Carol. "Jewish Customs and Traditional Foods" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 14, 1978 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/6 Hughel, Donald Ray Jr. "The Contrasting Techniques of Two Rural Women in Preserving Food" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Shelby County, Flat Rock), F101, Alexander, 2nd Summer Session 1981 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/7 Lewis, Jan. "Over Their Dead Bodies" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F220, Instructor Unknown, August 10, 1980 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/8 Krueckeberg, Judy. "Diet Habits" (North America, Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F101, April 2, 1981 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/9 Washauer, Bruce. "Fishing on Lake Wawasee" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F220, Gary Stanton, Summer Session 1982 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/10 Siner, Jeffrey. "Water Witching" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Putnam County, Greencastle), F101, Janelli, November 30, 1984 (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/11 Mitchell, Anthony R. "The Use and Lore of Coon Dogs in South-Central Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown (Analog audio cassette removed and stored separately in box 10), Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C 85/12 Martin, May Neil. "Old Southern Indiana Hunting Techniques" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Perry County, Tell City), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 22, 1977 (Box 9)
  - M/C 86/001 Retish, Josh. "The Jewish Talit," F101, John Johnson, 1986 (Box 9)
  - M/C 86/002 Edwards, Scott. "Headstones" (North America, U.S., Hamilton County) F101, Warren Roberts, 1987 (Box 9)
  - M/C 86/003 Raymond, Claire. "Spinning and Weaving," F101, John Johnson, Fall 1986 (Box 9)
  - M/C 87/001 Woodall, Dana. "Weaving," F101, Barbara Truesdell, April 17, 1987 (Box 9)
  - M/C 87/002 Nash, Tamra. "Quilting," F101, Instructor Unknown, April 16, 1987 (Box 9)
  - M/C 87/003 Parks, Mikie. "Traditional Family Foodways," F220, Hanna Griff, Summer 1987 (Box 9)
  - M/C 87/004 Forbes, J. Thomas. "Fraternity Dress," F101, Instructor Unknown, 1987 (Box 9)
  - M/C 87/005 Brooks, Peggy. "Charlie the Chairmaker," F220, Paul Tyler, 1987 (Box 9)
  - M/C 88/001 Allard, Bruce. "Gravestone Art in Monroe County," F101, Hasan El-Shamy, Spring 1988 (Box 9)
  - M/C 88/002 Bodnar, Lori. "Yard Art as Folk Art" (North America, U.S., Orange County, Paoli), F220, Hanna Griff, Summer 1988 (Box 9)
  - M/C Mossbrucker, Mike. "Matthews Mansion", Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Roger Beatty, A.I., Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Okerson, Jim. "Folklore of a Covered Bridge," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Burnett, Neal. "Trapping Folklore Project," Class # Unknown, Eric Montenyohl, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Kimbrough, David L. "Rattlesnake Hunting in Texas," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Alexander, Dawn Marie. No Title, Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Bowers, Jim. "The Art of Old-Fashioned Broom-making," Class # Unknown, Gary Stanton, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Durham, Deborah. "A Bloomington Limestone Carver: A Folk Artist'sCreativity Within a Traditional Society," F391, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Lutes, Linda D. "American Needlecraft," F220, Carol Edwards, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Todd, Janda. "Railroad - Madison, Indiana [Photographs only]" Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Pope, James. "Quilts" Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Miller, Lee. "Tombstones" Course Unknown, Carol Edwards, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Heck, Richard G. "One of the Oldest Standing Houses in Southern Indiana" C391, Warren Roberts, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Unknown. "Ole Steffan Dahl" Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - M/C Krepshaw, John. "Tombstones and Epitaphs" F101, El Shamy, Date Unknown (Box 9)
- Restricted files, (1 folder) (Box 10)
- Fieldwork cassette tapes
  - M/C 76/8 Vanderwerp, Mary. "Persimmon Pudding" CT-A010, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 77/29 Miller, Bruce R. "The Nashville House" CT-A021, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 77/60 Freer, Lisa. "Folklore" MC-77/60, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 78/5 Black, Judith Ellen. "Interview with Cindy Gerner Contemporary Quilt-maker" CT-78/35, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 78/6 Brady, Holly. "Transmission of Recipes..." CT-A033, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 78/12 Duckworth, Ginny. "Food Preservation" CT-A045, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 78/15 Trittipo, Salinda J. "Folklore Interview - Quilting" CT-78/36, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 78/16 Kelly, Amy. "...Dutch Cooking" CT-A047, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 78/17 Fhiemann, Carole E. "Covered Bridges in Parke Co." CT-A048, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 78/18 Headley, Steve. "Crafts of the Farrier" CT-A050, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/1 Raab, Jerry. "Old-Fashioned Hog Butchering", genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/8 Cody, Rick Gerald. "Basket Making" CT-A068, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/10 Pratt, Donna F. "Cabinet Making" CT-A071, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/11 Masaw, Angie. "Horse-shoeing: Historical Anal." CT-A073, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/12 Doug Hasler., (3 tapes) (Box 10)
    - "...Threshing" Tape 1 CT-A073, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
    - "...Threshing" Tape 2 CT-A074, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
    - "...Threshing" Tape 3 CT-A075, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/19 Elsner, Lisa. "Crochet" CT-A077, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/21 Schroer, Cande. "Quilts: Classification & Tech." CT-A078, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/22 Hornbach, Theresa. "Quilting Patterns" CT-A079, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/25 Sichting, Cheryl. "Comparison of Quilters" CT-A094, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/26 Sanders, Jamie. "Maple Sugaring" CT-A093, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 79/30 Kleopfer, Eric G. "Monroe Co. Tombstones" CT-A095, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 80/7 Fee, Kathryn. "Maple Syrup" CT-A105, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 80/8 Cox, Anne-Marie. "Seat Weaving" CT-A106, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 80/9 Edging, Thomas. "Hog Butchering" CT-A107, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 80/14 Sitek, Frances Arlene., (2 tapes) (Box 10)
    - "...Folk Cookery" Tape 1 CT-A114, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
    - "...Folk Cookery" Tape 2 CT-A115, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 81/4 Reichard, Katie. "German Christmas Cooking" CT-A119, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 81/15 Salzmann, Jean., (2 tapes) (Box 10)
    - "Quilting Group Meeting" Salzman #1, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
    - "Quilting Group Meeting" Salzman #2, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)
  - M/C 85/1 Gibbs, Diana. "Indiana Folklore Term Paper - Cattle Breeding", genreform: ¼" analog open reel tape (Box 10)
  - M/C 85/11 Mitchell, Anthony R. "...Coon Dogs" CT-A134, genreform: analog audio cassette (Box 10)